WJZ-TV Collection R0129.WJZ R0129.WJZ
Stage
- Documentary Specials, DOCS
  - Marked for Glory, 1964-04-02; GLORY; 57 Reels Print overs, work prints, negative trims and overs Film: 16mm
    Documentary special produced by WJZ-TV about the life of F. Scott Fitzgerald, who resided in Baltimore during his wife's treatment at the Sheppard-Pratt Hospital in Towson.
  - The Cooping, 1964-11; COOP; 6 Reels Magnetic track, Negatives Film: 16mm
    WJZ-TV produced thirty-minute documentary special on the death of the famed Baltimore resident, Edgar Allan Poe.
- The Arnold Zenker Show, 1970; ZENKR; 2 Cassettes Show dubs 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic
  Arnold Zenker is a media broadcaster who worked with ABC and hosted a daily talk-variety television show on WJZ-13 in the 1970s.
- Quiz Shows, QUIZS
  - Kids Baffle, 1981-1988; KIDSB; 47 Cassettes
    Hosted by Bob Callahan, this children's show featured local junior high schools competing academically.
  - Quiz Kids, QZKDS
  - It's Academic, 1990; ACDEM; 4 Reels Dub 1 inch videotape
    A WJZ-TV local high school academic game show.
- Demo reels, 1980-1985; reels; 62 Cassettes Betacam, 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic, 1/4 inch audio tape
  Short audiovisual demo or sampling of a professional broadcast journalist's work, either of potential employees for WJZ-TV or employees applying for journalism awards.
- Lottery, 1983-1984; LOTRY; 14 Cassettes 1 inch videotape, 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic
  Televised picking of the Maryland State Lottery.
- Visit to Peyton Place, 1965-09; PEYTN; 5 Reels Reversal, A, B, and C Rolls Film: 16mm
  Produced by WJZ-TV, Alan Smith interviewing the stars of the ABC dramatic serial "Peyton Place" on the 20th Century-Fox Lot in Hollywood.
- Shakedown, 1986-1992; SHAKED; 88 Cassettes; 8 Reels 1 inch videotape
  "Shakedown" was a dance show featuring local teen talent as an attempt to revive the local interest of the original "Buddy Deane Show," which ran from 1957 to 1964 on WJZ.
  - Shakedown Field Tape: Odell's Nightclub, 1985; WJZ-UNKN-104-001 (Mixed materials 104, Tape 1)
- Miscellaneous Footage, 1965-1993; MISC; 3640 Cassettes; 22 Reels 2 inch videotape: Quad; 8 Reels 1 inch videotape
  Moving images whose series are unknown or unidentified as of yet.
  - Baltimore Riots Reel, 1968-04
    Shot List
    1. Spiro Agnew discussing state of emergency in Baltimore City and Baltimore County, curfews, and executive orders 2. Street scenes in aftermath of riots 3. D'Alesandro press conference on the riots 4. General Gelston press conference on the riots 5. D'Alesandro press conference on the riots and proclamations 6. Traffic and street scenes, putting out fires, burned out buildings: Attman's Delicatessen 7. Unknown business owner interviewed 8. Supermarket owner or employee interviewed 9. Unknown man and woman interviewed about looting 10. Press conference with civil rights leader on his meeting with Spiro Agnew and the intent to divide the black community 11. Street scenes, people sweeping sidewalks 12. Unknown man on insurance coverage after looting 13. People in line for food distribution 14. Unknown man on hope for the future and lessons learned 15. Press conference with D'Alesandro and others on the restoration of law and order 16. Unknown man on agencies and disaster relief services for refugees 17. Press conference with D'Alesandro
  - 24 Hours: Sphinx Club, 1988; WJZ-UNKN-044-021 (Mixed materials 44, Tape 21)
  - Unknown Program Field Tape, 1988-05-13; WJZ-UNKN-035-005 (Mixed materials 35, Tape 5)
  - Baltimore, 1948…WJZ13 Forty Something!, 1988; FORTY; 1 Cassettes Dub: distribution VHS
    A program made by WJZ-TV about the history of WJZ-TV.
  - Come and Meet the Music, MUSIC; 2 Cassettes 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic
  - These Other Americans, OTHER; 42 Reels Dub Film: 16mm
  - German Scene, 1991; SCENE; 5 Reels Film: 16mm
    Most likely dubs of a Maryland Public Television show.
  - Real to Reel, REAL2; 1 Cassettes 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic
  - Straight Out, STRGT; 1 Cassettes 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic
  - Joe Lombardo Show, JOELO; 1 Cassettes 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic
  - The Jones and West Show, 1988; JONES; 4 Reels 1/4 inch audio tape
    Radio program.
  - Mike Douglas Show, 1979; MIKED; 2 Cassettes Dub 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic
    A Group W talk show nationally broadcast from 1963 to 1982.
- People are Talking, 1982-1988; PAT; 179 Cassettes; 1 Reels 1 inch videotape
  A local talk show which premiered August 14, 1978, originally hosted by Oprah Winfrey and Richard Sher.
- Tape Library, TPLIB
  Stock footage library used by the station.
- In the Spotlight, 1988-1989; SPOTL; 35 Cassettes; 1 Reels 1 inch videotape
- Spotlight, 1988-1989; SLGHT; 4 Reels Master: edited, Dub 1 inch videotape
- Commercial Spots, SPOTS; 700 Cassettes Ampex ACR-25 cartridge 2 inch videotape: Quad
- Evening Magazine, 1977-09-12; WJZ-EVMAG-002-002 (Mixed materials 2, Tape 2)
  - Evening Show, 1977-09-12; WJZ-EVMAG-002-002-01 (Mixed materials 2, Tape 2, Segment 1)